ARJUN SURESH KM

OBJECTIVE

I'm a Machine Learning Intern and Python Full Stack Developer with a strong background in creating advanced solutions and analyzing data to achieve great results. I've developed a recommender system that increased customer engagement by 30% and used machine learning to gain valuable insights. My skills in Python, JavaScript, and MongoDB, combined with a Master's in Computer Application, make me well-suited for roles that need both technical expertise and a knack for innovation. I'm adaptable and experienced in fullstack web development, making me a valuable team member.

EXPERIENCE HISTORY

Machine learning - intern at prinston smart engineers, banglore

JULY 2024 - PRESENT

- Used machine learning algorithms to identify and classify large datasets, resulting in actionable insights for business stakeholders
- Implemented advanced analytics techniques such as linear and logistic regression to identify correlations and predict outcomes

Python Full Stack Development at Quest innovative solutions, kannur, kerala

OCTOBER 2021 – FEBRUARY 2022

- Developed a full stack web application using modern technologies such as Flask, Django, and MongoDB
- Used HTML, CSS and JavaScript to create interactive elements that improved user experience
- Developed a web application using Python and Django that improved scalability and reliability

PROJECTS

Cartoon Tv

This project aims to provide cartoon videos and stories for kids

On Road Vehicle Assistance (Group project)

This project aims to provide support for vehicle breakdowns

Hair Style Recommendation System (Group project)

This project provides hairstyle recommendations for the user based on their face shapes

EDUCATION

(MCA)Master of computer application, krupanidhi college of management,

Banglore

NOVEMBER 2022 – NOVEMBER 2024

(BCA)Bachelor of computer application, Sreenarayana college, Calicut

JULY 2018 - APRIL 2021

Details

Bengaluru India

6282452018

Arjunsuresh62000@gmail.com Linkedin Github

Skills

SQL

JavaScripts MySQL HTML PHP CSS

Python DataAnalysis MongoDB

Numpy

Pandas